<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ancient Greek Quotes</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="info_menu">Application Info</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Quotes</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="share_quote">Share Quote</string>
    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>
    <string name="menu_info">Info</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="bertrand_russell">Bertrand Russell</string>


    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item name="Aristotle">"Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Aristotle">"Dignity does not consist in possessing honors, but in deserving them."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Aristotle">"You will never do anything in this world without courage. It is the greatest quality of the mind next to honor."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Aristotle">"The life of money making is one undertaken under compulsion, and wealth is evidently not the good we are seeking; for it is merely useful and for the sake of something else."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plotinus">"Knowledge, if it does not determine action, is dead to us."-Plotinus</item>
        <item name="Herodotus">"Great deeds are usually wrought at great risks."-Herodotus</item>
        <item name="Herodotus">"Haste in every business brings failures."-Herodotus</item>
        <item name="Demosthenes">"Beware the barrenness of a busy life."-Demosthenes</item>
        <item name="Demosthenes">"The only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing."-Demosthenes</item>
        <item name="Epictetus">"Wealth consists not in having great possessions, but in having few wants."-Epictetus</item>
        <item name="Epictetus">"Make the best use of what's in your power and take the rest as it happens."-Epictetus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"A good decision is based on knowledge and not numbers."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Better a little which is well done, than a great deal imperfectly."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The beginning is the most important part of the work."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Apply yourself both now and in the next life. Without effort, you cannot be prosperous. Though the land be good, you cannot have an abundant crop without cultivation."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"He who is not a good servant will not be a good master."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"As the builders say, the larger stones do not lie well without the lesser."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Man is the measure of all things."-Protagoras</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Man is the dream of a shadow."-Pindar</item>
        <item name="Plato">"As mortals we should behave as mortals."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Man: one who thinks of what he sees."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"It is not possible to know medicine without knowing what a human is."-Hippocrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"What a wonderful being is the man if he is a man."-Menander</item>
        <item name="Plato">"We became men once and one cannot become twice."-Epicurus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Man is a microcosm."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Man is naturally deceitful ever, in every way!"-Aristophanes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Most people are bad."-Bias of Priene</item>
        <item name="Plato">"World is decay, life is perception."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"This world, which is the same for all, has not been made by any god or man, but it always has been, is, and will be an ever living fire."-Heraclitus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"One word brings another."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"There are countless worlds both born and perishable."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Place is the greatest thing, as it contains all things."-Thales of Miletus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Nothing bad is without something good."-Ancient Greek phrase</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Pleasure, a most mighty lure to evil."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The good can never mix with the evil."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The just man is most free from disturbance, while the unjust is full of the utmost disturbance."-Epicurus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Life is short and Art long; the opportunity fleeting, experience deceitful, and judgment difficult."-Hippocrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Nobody lives the life he chooses to live."-Menander</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Like in a statue, all parts of a life must be beautiful."-Socrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"How sweet is life when fortune is not envious."-Menander</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Life is short."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The art of life is more like the wrestler's art than the dancer's, in respect of this, that it should stand ready and firm to meet onsets which are sudden and unexpected."-Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Death is nothing to us. Because something which is decomposed has no senses while something without senses is nothing to us."-Epicurus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Better a bad life than a good death."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"If gods do evil, they are not gods."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Nothing is clear to men about the gods."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"If it’s not right, don’t do it; if it’s not true, don’t say it."-Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The “right” is nothing more than what benefits the powerful."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"A wrongdoer is often a man who has left something undone, not always one who has done something."-Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item name="Plato">"What Zeus? Do not trifle. There is no Zeus."-Aristophanes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"We know nothing for sure. Because the truth is hidden in the deep."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The words of the truth are simple."-Aeschylus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Everything flows, nothing stands still."-Heraclitus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Pleasures are transient, honors are immortal."-Periander of Corinth</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Knowing that human happiness never remains long in the same place."-Herodotus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"And you, old man, we are told you prospered once."-Homer</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The universe is change; our life is what our thoughts make it."-Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Do not act as if you are going to live ten thousand years. The inevitable hangs over you. As long as you live, while it is in your power, be good."-Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The now is a sort of a middle thing."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Know the right time."-Pittacus of Mytilene</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Respond on time."-Periander of Corinth</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Life is short and Art long; the opportunity fleeting, experience deceitful, and judgment difficult."-Hippocrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Time is the healer of all inevitable ills."-Menander</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Time is that wherein there is opportunity, and opportunity is that wherein there is no great time"-Hippocrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Time will explain it all. He is a talker, and needs no questioning before he speaks."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Use time sparingly."-Chilon of Sparta</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Since life is short, don’t make it long with bad deeds."-Thales of Miletus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"A huge tree can tower from a tiny seed."-Aeschylus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"If you want to live a life without stress, consider whatever is going to happen in the future as if it has already happened"-Epictetus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The old man has been young, whilst it is unknown if the young man will reach old age."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Everything comes from earth and everything ends in earth."-Xenophanes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"AWe are indebted to our parents for living, but to our teachers for living well."-Alexander the Great</item>
        <item name="Plato">"To think, to see, to understand, to show the arse, to trick, to suspect the worst, to question everything."-Aristophanes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Practice is everything."-Aeschylus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Better be a late learner than an ignorant."-Socrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Three things support the perfection of a man: character, learning and practice."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Education needs these three: natural endowment, study, practice."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"If you do not hit the clay, you cannot make tile."-Archytas</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The beginning of everything is atoms and void, and everything else is perception."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Things do not look the same when viewed from far or near."-Euripides</item>
        <item name="Plato">"He who is close to Zeus is close to thunder."-Aesop</item>
        <item name="Plato">"For the wise is easy to go anywhere. Because the whole world is home for a good soul."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The beginning is half of everything."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"In the beginning there was chaos."-Hesiod</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Wickedness and injustice are intentional."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Slaves and master could never be friends."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Soon, you will forget everything, and soon everybody will forget you."-Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item name="Plato">"One cannot evade destiny."-Ancient Greek phrase</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Much learning does not teach the mind."-Heraclitus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Everything in excess is opposed to nature."-Hippocrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The first and greatest victory is to conquer yourself; to be conquered by yourself is of all things most shameful and vile."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Nobody loves anybody more than himself."-Menander</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Character is destiny."-Heraclitus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Don’t ask who is now, but who he has always been."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Character lies in polite and friendly speaking."-Aesop</item>
        <item name="Plato">"It’s not easy to change a bad character."-Menander</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Habit is second nature."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Man is by nature a political animal."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Friendship is one soul living in two bodies."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Happiness comes from the soul, like unhappiness."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Each art must use its tools, each body its soul."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Mind is the swiftest of things, for it runs through everything."-Thales of Miletus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The opinions of men are toys for boys."-Heraclitus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Nothing is easier than self-deceit. For what a man wishes to be true, he generally believes to be true."-Demosthenes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"A fool laughs even when there is nothing funny."-Pittacus of Mytilene</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Don't laugh too much, neither with many things, nor too loud."-Epictetus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Beauty is better than any recommendation letter."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Who is happy? This is a person, who has a healthy body, is dowered with peace of mind and cultivates his talents."-Thales of Miletus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Do not trust good luck."-Chilon of Sparta</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Men have made an idol of Fortune as an excuse for their own lack of willpower."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The unlucky man will be bitten even by a sheep."-Aesop</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Nobody can escape destiny."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Donkeys prefer garbage to gold."-Heraclitus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"In all things of nature there is something of the marvelous."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"If I were not Alexander, I should wish to be Diogenes."-Alexander the Great</item>
        <item name="Plato">"And you, son Brutus?"-Julius Caesar</item>
        <item name="Plato">"No one likes one whom he fears."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"One who thinks right is better than myriads who think wrong."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"To the strongest!"-Alexander the Great</item>
        <item name="Plato">"War is a school for virtue."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Virtue consists not in avoiding wrong-doing, but in having no want for it."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The continent man is not he who avoids pleasure, but having tasted it, is not carried to excess."-Aristippus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"No one is free if he cannot subdue himself."-Epictetus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Whoever knows about tragedy, knows about epics too."-Aristotle,</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The investigation of the meaning of words is the beginning of wisdom."-Antisthenes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Medicine heals the body and wisdom removes the suffering from the souls."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"That man is wise who can say what he wants in a minimum of words."-Aristophanes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"We must help the poor, not encourage idleness."-Solon</item>
        <item name="Plato">"I know that I know nothing."-Socrates</item>
        <item name="Plato">"It is better to conceal ignorance than to expose it."-Heraclitus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Women are more envious and more querulous than men."-Aristotle</item>
        <item name="Plato">"You will not be tolerated if you are successful."-Aeschylus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"A man completely enslaved to money will never be just."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"The madness of love is the greatest of the blessings of the gods."-Plato</item>
        <item name="Plato">"We are indebted to our parents for living, but to our teachers for living well."-Alexander the Great</item>
        <item name="Plato">"When the lamp goes off, all the women are the same."-Diogenes</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Put more trust in integrity of character than in an oath."-Solon</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Don’t trust everybody."-Pittacus of Mytilene</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Hard work is the father of good reputation."-Ancient Greek proverb</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Hear much, speak to the point."-Bias of Priene</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Do not let your tongue outrun your mind."-Chilon of Sparta</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Speaking is the shadow of action."-Democritus</item>
        <item name="Plato">"Helen? Ship destroyer, men destroyer, city destroyer."-Aeschylus</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="favorites">
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"The fundamental cause of the trouble is that in the modern world the stupid are cocksure while the intelligent are full of doubt." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Of all forms of caution, caution in love is perhaps the most fatal to true happiness." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"To fear love is to fear life, and those who fear life are already 3-parts dead." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"I would never die for my beliefs because I might be wrong." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"A stupid man's report of what a clever man says can never be accurate, because he unconsciously translates what he hears into something he can understand." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Science may set limits to knowledge, but should not set limits to imagination." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Love is wise, hatred is foolish." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Men are born ignorant, not stupid; they are made stupid by education." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Whoever wishes to become a philosopher must learn not to be frightened by absurdities." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Do not fear to be eccentric in opinion, for every opinion now accepted was once eccentric." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"There are two motives for reading a book; one, that you enjoy it; the other, that you can boast about it." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Fear is the main source of superstition, and one of the main sources of cruelty. To conquer fear is the beginning of wisdom." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"The hardest thing to learn in life is which bridge to cross and which to burn." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"It's easy to fall in love. The hard part is finding someone to catch you." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"To teach how to live without certainty, and yet without being paralyzed by hesitation, is perhaps the chief thing that philosophy, in our age, can still do for those who study it." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Most people would sooner die than think; in fact, they do so." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"It is the preoccupation with possessions, more than anything else, that prevents us from living freely and nobly." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Those who have never known the deep intimacy and the intense companionship of happy mutual love have missed the best thing that life has to give." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"Collective fear stimulates herd instinct, and tends to produce ferocity toward those who are not regarded as members of the herd." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"It has been said that man is a rational animal. All my life I have been searching for evidence which could support this." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"No one gossips about other people’s secret virtues." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"We know very little, and yet it is astonishing that we know so much, and still more astonishing that so little knowledge can give us so much power." - Bertrand Russell</item>
        <item name="Bertrand Russell">"The secret of happiness is very simply this: let your interests be as wide as possible, and let your reactions to the things and persons that interest you be as far as possible friendly rather than hostile." - Bertrand Russell</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

</resources>
